safesecuretrial.com 2011-09-22

# Privacy Policy

We take your privacy seriously. This statement discloses the privacy practices of Smoke Freely on this website. By using this website, you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to the collection and use of information by Smoke Freely on this website, but does not apply to information that you may send to us by other means. Smoke Freely respects the privacy of visitors to our online sites. The kinds of information we collect from you will vary, depending on how you use our website. In order to take part in certain services on our website, you will be required to provide certain personal information (e.g., your name, address, e-mail address, mailing address, phone, etc.). In addition to the information you choose to submit, our systems are set up to gather certain anonymous data to help us better understand how our site is being used and how we can improve it. This automatically gathered data includes any content you view on our website. We will only collect personally identifiable data, such as your name, address, telephone number, mailing address and/or e-mail address, when it is voluntarily submitted to us at this website. Smoke Freely and/or the companies we hire will use this information to comply with your request for information or as otherwise disclosed to you at the location at which you submit your information. From time to time, we may refer to that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services. We may use that information to contact you. We may collect the aforementioned information through both online and offline means. Information collected both online and offline may be combined and shared with our marketing partners, advertisers, and other third parties. We may use information collected from recipients of our marketing campaigns, visitors to our websites, and our marketing partners, advertisers, and other third parties for any of the following purposes in either the online or offline arena:

To provide individuals with targeted offers based on their specific requests or their stated preference to receive certain categories of offers; 

To send individuals information and promotional materials from our company as well as from our marketing partners, advertisers, and other third parties; 

To deliver targeted display advertisements and offers through online marketing communications, such as emails, banner advertisements, and pop-up advertisements (by matching criteria provided by our advertisers with information collected from our visitors); 

To enable our marketing partners, advertisers, and other third parties to communicate with individuals; 

To administer contests and sweepstakes offered on our websites, other web pages, or on our partners' websites; 

To contact visitors to our websites or registered members of our marketing campaigns when necessary; 

To help address problems with our websites or marketing services; 

To administer our websites; 

To conduct internal reviews of our websites (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to specific pages within the site); 

To help us better understand recipients of our marketing campaigns and visitors' use of our websites; and 

To protect the security or integrity of our websites and other web pages that are accessible through our online marketing campaigns. Non-personal information will be used for these purposes as well as for conducting internal reviews and monitoring of our websites and other web pages that are accessible through our online marketing campaigns and providing a greater online experience for our visitors. 

This Smoke Freely website is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 18. 

We do not collect personally identifiable data from any person we know to be under the age of 18. 

You can always choose not to provide personal information, even though it might be needed to take advantage of Smoke Freely offers or website features. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other communications from us or if you wish to check your personal information, please contact us.
